每件东西都摆放齐整  位置妥当
Everything else is perfectly ordered, managed.
简直跟强迫症一样  无意冒犯
The whole thing's verging on OCD. My respects.
这个小雕像在清洁工每次打扫过之后
This figurine is routinely repositioned after
都要重新归位
the cleaner's been in,
这幅照片每天也都要仔细摆放
this picture is straightened every day,
但却有个这么难看的空缺
yet this ugly gap remains.
-少了件东西  而且是最近才少的  -对
- Something's missing from here, but only recently. - Yes, a...
-石膏像  -石膏像
- Plaster bust. - ..Plaster bust.
那又怎么了  石膏像打碎了
Oh, for God's sake! It got broken.
跟查理有什么关系
What the hell has this got to do with Charlie?
-地毯  -什么
- Rug! - What?
这东西怎么会碎呢
Well, how could it get broken?
唯一的可能性就是掉在地上
The only place for it to fall is the floor
而这里却有块厚地毯
and there is a big thick rug.
-有关系吗  -韦尔斯伯鲁太太我非常抱歉
- Does it matter? - Mrs Welsborough, my apologies.
-让他问个明白非常重要  -你朋友疯了吧
- It is worth letting him do this. - Is your friend quite mad?